{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "e88ebf10-cb65-48ae-886e-d48ab14e1114", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Cameron's attempt to renegotiate the U.K.'s EU membership terms failed.'?", "option_A": "The referendum date was set in February.", "option_B": "None of the others are correct causes.", "option_C": "The Conservative Party won the election.", "option_D": "Prime Minister David Cameron pledged a referendum on EU membership in 2013.", "golden_answer": "B"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "c1e69548-4fdc-4a84-b1ee-118e1df0d3f1", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The United Kingdom held a referendum on June 23.'?", "option_A": "Cameron's attempt to renegotiate the U.K.'s EU membership terms failed.", "option_B": "The Conservative Party won the election.", "option_C": "Prime Minister David Cameron pledged a referendum on EU membership in 2013.", "option_D": "The nation divided into 'remain' and 'leave' camps.", "golden_answer": "B,C"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "09711de2-1bf7-4fb5-a1cb-ac99d744a408", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The United Kingdom held a referendum on June 23.'?", "option_A": "The nation divided into 'remain' and 'leave' camps.", "option_B": "Prime Minister David Cameron pledged a referendum on EU membership in 2013.", "option_C": "The Conservative Party won the election.", "option_D": "The referendum date was set in February.", "golden_answer": "B,C,D"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "a0374b9a-c69b-463b-b9f0-98db62f219d4", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Northern Ireland and Scotland voted to remain in the EU.'?", "option_A": "The Conservative Party won the election.", "option_B": "The UK voted to leave the EU in a June 23 referendum.", "option_C": "The referendum date was set in February.", "option_D": "None of the others are correct causes.", "golden_answer": "D"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "f119ff25-3615-48f2-bcb1-62fab8d4ac4f", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Northern Ireland and Scotland voted to remain in the EU.'?", "option_A": "The United Kingdom held a referendum on June 23.", "option_B": "The nation divided into 'remain' and 'leave' camps.", "option_C": "The referendum date was set in February.", "option_D": "The Conservative Party won the election.", "golden_answer": "A"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "b3b3eb8f-d619-4363-876e-51748b469673", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'David Cameron announced his resignation as Prime Minister.'?", "option_A": "The Conservative Party won the election.", "option_B": "The UK voted to leave the EU in a June 23 referendum.", "option_C": "The United Kingdom held a referendum on June 23.", "option_D": "Northern Ireland and Scotland voted to remain in the EU.", "golden_answer": "B,C"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "fe1621a3-57a4-4381-8620-16633f43690d", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The British pound plunged in value.'?", "option_A": "The referendum date was set in February.", "option_B": "Northern Ireland and Scotland voted to remain in the EU.", "option_C": "Cameron's attempt to renegotiate the U.K.'s EU membership terms failed.", "option_D": "None of the others are correct causes.", "golden_answer": "D"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "7c9496f7-e853-4c57-8fc9-19cc878c4f05", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The British pound plunged in value.'?", "option_A": "Cameron's attempt to renegotiate the U.K.'s EU membership terms failed.", "option_B": "The referendum date was set in February.", "option_C": "The UK voted to leave the EU in a June 23 referendum.", "option_D": "The United Kingdom held a referendum on June 23.", "golden_answer": "C,D"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "ebb59425-5583-4678-960a-7dce551da472", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The British pound plunged in value.'?", "option_A": "The nation divided into 'remain' and 'leave' camps.", "option_B": "Prime Minister David Cameron pledged a referendum on EU membership in 2013.", "option_C": "The UK voted to leave the EU in a June 23 referendum.", "option_D": "The referendum date was set in February.", "golden_answer": "C"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "b3a5fe62-6b61-4617-8f7d-801cb1ae13ac", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Global markets plunged following the Brexit vote.'?", "option_A": "Cameron's attempt to renegotiate the U.K.'s EU membership terms failed.", "option_B": "Northern Ireland and Scotland voted to remain in the EU.", "option_C": "The referendum date was set in February.", "option_D": "None of the others are correct causes.", "golden_answer": "D"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "9da849c7-b01d-4679-990a-da948c44a451", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Global markets plunged following the Brexit vote.'?", "option_A": "Cameron's attempt to renegotiate the U.K.'s EU membership terms failed.", "option_B": "David Cameron announced his resignation as Prime Minister.", "option_C": "The UK voted to leave the EU in a June 23 referendum.", "option_D": "Northern Ireland and Scotland voted to remain in the EU.", "golden_answer": "C"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "b952f4f0-c7b9-4bce-ac07-000778c7d169", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Global markets plunged following the Brexit vote.'?", "option_A": "The referendum date was set in February.", "option_B": "The UK voted to leave the EU in a June 23 referendum.", "option_C": "Cameron's attempt to renegotiate the U.K.'s EU membership terms failed.", "option_D": "The United Kingdom held a referendum on June 23.", "golden_answer": "B,D"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "a412c8d1-144e-4d4f-b2c0-d6097c6dc32e", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Nicola Sturgeon stated the Scottish government would prepare legislation for a new independence referendum.'?", "option_A": "The referendum date was set in February.", "option_B": "Global markets plunged following the Brexit vote.", "option_C": "None of the others are correct causes.", "option_D": "The nation divided into 'remain' and 'leave' camps.", "golden_answer": "C"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "e4f3ab11-c26f-4ac5-b4c2-9461a1a389fc", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Nicola Sturgeon stated the Scottish government would prepare legislation for a new independence referendum.'?", "option_A": "The nation divided into 'remain' and 'leave' camps.", "option_B": "The UK voted to leave the EU in a June 23 referendum.", "option_C": "Global markets plunged following the Brexit vote.", "option_D": "The British pound plunged in value.", "golden_answer": "B"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "8aad1301-b6a5-4425-98ca-6bb566bd78fd", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Sinn Fein called for a referendum on Irish unity.'?", "option_A": "The referendum date was set in February.", "option_B": "None of the others are correct causes.", "option_C": "Prime Minister David Cameron pledged a referendum on EU membership in 2013.", "option_D": "David Cameron announced his resignation as Prime Minister.", "golden_answer": "B"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "0d46c0bc-fbba-485c-8660-1719ea597241", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Sinn Fein called for a referendum on Irish unity.'?", "option_A": "The UK voted to leave the EU in a June 23 referendum.", "option_B": "David Cameron announced his resignation as Prime Minister.", "option_C": "The United Kingdom held a referendum on June 23.", "option_D": "The referendum date was set in February.", "golden_answer": "A,C"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "e29d933b-b064-4e95-abed-5b0f8b289220", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Sinn Fein called for a referendum on Irish unity.'?", "option_A": "The British pound plunged in value.", "option_B": "The Conservative Party won the election.", "option_C": "The referendum date was set in February.", "option_D": "The UK voted to leave the EU in a June 23 referendum.", "golden_answer": "D"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "1adf6d15-976a-48db-891a-e2c555300649", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Over three million Brits called for a do-over.'?", "option_A": "None of the others are correct causes.", "option_B": "Cameron's attempt to renegotiate the U.K.'s EU membership terms failed.", "option_C": "Prime Minister David Cameron pledged a referendum on EU membership in 2013.", "option_D": "The Conservative Party won the election.", "golden_answer": "A"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "f817cc59-73f2-4c6e-a593-a469ef98bdcc", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Over three million Brits called for a do-over.'?", "option_A": "The United Kingdom held a referendum on June 23.", "option_B": "The UK voted to leave the EU in a June 23 referendum.", "option_C": "Cameron's attempt to renegotiate the U.K.'s EU membership terms failed.", "option_D": "Prime Minister David Cameron pledged a referendum on EU membership in 2013.", "golden_answer": "A,B"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "a66566ce-8f8a-4419-a47d-14e1dc491bc9", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Over three million Brits called for a do-over.'?", "option_A": "The Conservative Party won the election.", "option_B": "The UK voted to leave the EU in a June 23 referendum.", "option_C": "Sinn Fein called for a referendum on Irish unity.", "option_D": "The nation divided into 'remain' and 'leave' camps.", "golden_answer": "B"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "a46e778f-952f-4bec-9fed-e18efdec3e09", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The UK drafted the EU Counter Terrorism Strategy in 2005.'?", "option_A": "The British pound plunged in value.", "option_B": "None of the others are correct causes.", "option_C": "Sinn Fein called for a referendum on Irish unity.", "option_D": "The UK voted to leave the EU in a June 23 referendum.", "golden_answer": "B"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "c7534617-defc-4f65-a4ae-feb5c79b8659", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The UK influenced EU initiatives, including the Europol Counter Terrorism Centre (CTC) and the PNRD.'?", "option_A": "The Conservative Party won the election.", "option_B": "None of the others are correct causes.", "option_C": "Global markets plunged following the Brexit vote.", "option_D": "The UK voted to leave the EU in a June 23 referendum.", "golden_answer": "B"}
{"topic_id": 1, "uuid": "bd4c50ff-e6ad-48fb-b698-3fef6312a855", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The UK joined the Schengen Information System.'?", "option_A": "The UK influenced EU initiatives, including the Europol Counter Terrorism Centre (CTC) and the PNRD.", "option_B": "The nation divided into 'remain' and 'leave' camps.", "option_C": "None of the others are correct causes.", "option_D": "The UK voted to leave the EU in a June 23 referendum.", "golden_answer": "C"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "86eafcd9-889a-4627-803e-c83f01023054", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Supporters stormed the U.S. Capitol.'?", "option_A": "Protesters clashed with police and breached security barriers at the Capitol.", "option_B": "Trump urged supporters to march to the Capitol.", "option_C": "Trump supporters protested in Washington, D.C.", "option_D": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "golden_answer": "A,B,C"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "329df6ae-03cd-4376-b69c-dfaecd143ad9", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The House and Senate recessed, and the Capitol was locked down.'?", "option_A": "Protesters clashed with police and breached security barriers at the Capitol.", "option_B": "Trump supporters protested in Washington, D.C.", "option_C": "Supporters stormed the U.S. Capitol.", "option_D": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "golden_answer": "A,B,C"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "772a890f-6353-493c-9cdd-f7f8616ad82d", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Five people died during the riots.'?", "option_A": "Trump addressed the crowd.", "option_B": "Trump urged supporters to march to the Capitol.", "option_C": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "option_D": "None of the others are correct causes.", "golden_answer": "D"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "dba445c1-d712-498e-a112-ae254b72d1ce", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Five people died during the riots.'?", "option_A": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "option_B": "Trump urged supporters to march to the Capitol.", "option_C": "Trump addressed the crowd.", "option_D": "Supporters stormed the U.S. Capitol.", "golden_answer": "D"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "a9dc13ff-4922-4c05-bb93-d0ba718a7f75", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The congressional certification of Joe Biden’s victory was halted.'?", "option_A": "A woman was shot inside the Capitol and died.", "option_B": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "option_C": "Five people died during the riots.", "option_D": "None of the others are correct causes.", "golden_answer": "D"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "3cfcf026-da33-4453-a32e-e44162a8e116", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The congressional certification of Joe Biden’s victory was halted.'?", "option_A": "Supporters stormed the U.S. Capitol.", "option_B": "Trump supporters protested in Washington, D.C.", "option_C": "Protesters clashed with police and breached security barriers at the Capitol.", "option_D": "Five people died during the riots.", "golden_answer": "A,B,C"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "688b3b36-af34-4ebf-9efb-7202f681352e", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The congressional certification of Joe Biden’s victory was halted.'?", "option_A": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "option_B": "Five people died during the riots.", "option_C": "Trump urged supporters to march to the Capitol.", "option_D": "Protesters clashed with police and breached security barriers at the Capitol.", "golden_answer": "C,D"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "ac71e038-12a6-4364-97d6-1c669861d45a", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The congressional certification of Joe Biden’s victory was halted.'?", "option_A": "A woman was shot inside the Capitol and died.", "option_B": "Trump supporters protested in Washington, D.C.", "option_C": "Five people died during the riots.", "option_D": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "golden_answer": "B"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "afce6dc3-9c6f-46d9-99aa-d344c579b5c2", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The FBI and ATF cleared the Capitol.'?", "option_A": "Trump addressed the crowd.", "option_B": "None of the others are correct causes.", "option_C": "Five people died during the riots.", "option_D": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "golden_answer": "B"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "281794e8-b449-4de1-92d3-a4b223692cb1", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The FBI and ATF cleared the Capitol.'?", "option_A": "Five people died during the riots.", "option_B": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "option_C": "Supporters stormed the U.S. Capitol.", "option_D": "Trump addressed the crowd.", "golden_answer": "C"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "0938f60b-a3a7-481b-a7da-db69d0a7f97e", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The FBI and ATF cleared the Capitol.'?", "option_A": "Trump addressed the crowd.", "option_B": "Supporters stormed the U.S. Capitol.", "option_C": "Trump supporters protested in Washington, D.C.", "option_D": "Five people died during the riots.", "golden_answer": "B,C"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "373f8a7e-8544-4919-8c4c-4e00e8f56014", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Congress confirmed Biden as president in the early hours of January 7th.'?", "option_A": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "option_B": "None of the others are correct causes.", "option_C": "Five people died during the riots.", "option_D": "A woman was shot inside the Capitol and died.", "golden_answer": "B"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "15856f53-edee-4fcf-bd26-27d9f93fc40e", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Congress confirmed Biden as president in the early hours of January 7th.'?", "option_A": "The Capitol was secured, and lawmakers reconvened to continue certification.", "option_B": "The FBI and ATF cleared the Capitol.", "option_C": "A woman was shot inside the Capitol and died.", "option_D": "Five people died during the riots.", "golden_answer": "A,B"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "8c802ef0-db5c-47a2-ad28-782532d5b0c2", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Congress confirmed Biden as president in the early hours of January 7th.'?", "option_A": "The FBI and ATF cleared the Capitol.", "option_B": "Trump addressed the crowd.", "option_C": "Five people died during the riots.", "option_D": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "golden_answer": "A"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "e3f963b3-99a6-41c0-b061-1ac7614d49d0", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Capitol Police Chief Steven Sund, House Sergeant at Arms Paul Irving, and Senate Sergeant at Arms Michael Stenger resigned.'?", "option_A": "Congress confirmed Biden as president in the early hours of January 7th.", "option_B": "The House and Senate recessed, and the Capitol was locked down.", "option_C": "Supporters stormed the U.S. Capitol.", "option_D": "Protesters clashed with police and breached security barriers at the Capitol.", "golden_answer": "B,C,D"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "2ad825a7-e67f-4266-9ccb-c843bc5c1047", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Capitol Police Chief Steven Sund, House Sergeant at Arms Paul Irving, and Senate Sergeant at Arms Michael Stenger resigned.'?", "option_A": "Supporters stormed the U.S. Capitol.", "option_B": "The FBI and ATF cleared the Capitol.", "option_C": "Protesters clashed with police and breached security barriers at the Capitol.", "option_D": "Congress confirmed Biden as president in the early hours of January 7th.", "golden_answer": "A,C"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "77a83ef3-c77d-4286-92a2-886ceeb22c6d", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Twitter removed Trump's tweets and locked his account.'?", "option_A": "Capitol Police Chief Steven Sund, House Sergeant at Arms Paul Irving, and Senate Sergeant at Arms Michael Stenger resigned.", "option_B": "A woman was shot inside the Capitol and died.", "option_C": "None of the others are correct causes.", "option_D": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "golden_answer": "C"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "e954a7f3-8804-4204-8200-94cb4bf83c76", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Twitter removed Trump's tweets and locked his account.'?", "option_A": "A woman was shot inside the Capitol and died.", "option_B": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "option_C": "Supporters stormed the U.S. Capitol.", "option_D": "Capitol Police Chief Steven Sund, House Sergeant at Arms Paul Irving, and Senate Sergeant at Arms Michael Stenger resigned.", "golden_answer": "C"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "b27ef134-fe6a-4c92-b332-259f7c618410", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Trump was permanently banned from Twitter on January 8th.'?", "option_A": "Trump urged supporters to march to the Capitol.", "option_B": "Congress confirmed Biden as president in the early hours of January 7th.", "option_C": "A woman was shot inside the Capitol and died.", "option_D": "None of the others are correct causes.", "golden_answer": "D"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "08e19b71-e0c1-469d-8e08-11db613447d6", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Trump was permanently banned from Twitter on January 8th.'?", "option_A": "Five people died during the riots.", "option_B": "Trump urged supporters to march to the Capitol.", "option_C": "Supporters stormed the U.S. Capitol.", "option_D": "A woman was shot inside the Capitol and died.", "golden_answer": "C"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "430f412b-3279-4103-b971-73e42ee6b5e9", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Trump was impeached for a second time on January 13th.'?", "option_A": "The Capitol was secured, and lawmakers reconvened to continue certification.", "option_B": "None of the others are correct causes.", "option_C": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "option_D": "The D.C. National Guard was activated, and a citywide curfew was imposed.", "golden_answer": "B"}
{"topic_id": 3, "uuid": "aa49bbac-6e5c-48fc-8953-eb4f5fe137e6", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Trump was impeached for a second time on January 13th.'?", "option_A": "Capitol Police Chief Steven Sund, House Sergeant at Arms Paul Irving, and Senate Sergeant at Arms Michael Stenger resigned.", "option_B": "Trump addressed the crowd.", "option_C": "Pipe bombs were reported at the Republican National Committee building and the Democratic National Committee headquarters.", "option_D": "Supporters stormed the U.S. Capitol.", "golden_answer": "D"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "04b99022-c4e1-4d7a-af4c-17d3eda0a5bd", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Shinzo Abe reinterpreted Japan's constitution in 2014.'?", "option_A": "Shinzo Abe became the deputy chief cabinet secretary in the early 2000s.", "option_B": "Shinzo Abe returned to office in 2012 and later became the longest-serving prime minister.", "option_C": "None of the others are correct causes.", "option_D": "Shinzo Abe became the youngest prime minister in postwar Japan in 2006.", "golden_answer": "C"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "07f1263c-946d-42b6-a692-2409b0ad2ebe", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Benjamin Netanyahu visited Tokyo in 2014.'?", "option_A": "None of the others are correct causes.", "option_B": "Shinzo Abe reinterpreted Japan's constitution in 2014.", "option_C": "Shinzo Abe became the youngest prime minister in postwar Japan in 2006.", "option_D": "Shinzo Abe became the deputy chief cabinet secretary in the early 2000s.", "golden_answer": "A"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "a762bc7a-0f3a-48b5-88cc-f4e52cdd728d", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Shinzo Abe coined the phrase 'a free and open Indo-Pacific'.'?", "option_A": "Benjamin Netanyahu visited Tokyo in 2014.", "option_B": "Shinzo Abe returned to office in 2012 and later became the longest-serving prime minister.", "option_C": "None of the others are correct causes.", "option_D": "Shinzo Abe became the deputy chief cabinet secretary in the early 2000s.", "golden_answer": "C"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "0a88865a-36ff-4bf1-8a1a-e5d538f610e1", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Shinzo Abe promoted the Quadrilateral Security Dialogue (Quad).'?", "option_A": "None of the others are correct causes.", "option_B": "Shinzo Abe became the deputy chief cabinet secretary in the early 2000s.", "option_C": "Shinzo Abe became the youngest prime minister in postwar Japan in 2006.", "option_D": "Benjamin Netanyahu visited Tokyo in 2014.", "golden_answer": "A"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "e2165504-926e-4bc0-a35a-8a401634337c", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Shinzo Abe offered to host a peace summit in 2017.'?", "option_A": "None of the others are correct causes.", "option_B": "Shinzo Abe became the deputy chief cabinet secretary in the early 2000s.", "option_C": "Shinzo Abe promoted the Quadrilateral Security Dialogue (Quad).", "option_D": "Shinzo Abe coined the phrase 'a free and open Indo-Pacific'.", "golden_answer": "A"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "f8aa5d0a-2281-40fb-825d-9b754a66353a", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Shinzo Abe visited Jerusalem in 2018.'?", "option_A": "Shinzo Abe coined the phrase 'a free and open Indo-Pacific'.", "option_B": "Shinzo Abe reinterpreted Japan's constitution in 2014.", "option_C": "Shinzo Abe became the deputy chief cabinet secretary in the early 2000s.", "option_D": "None of the others are correct causes.", "golden_answer": "D"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "6d9a71fb-747c-4c13-9729-13a602ac9c33", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Yoshihide Suga succeeded Shinzo Abe in September 2020.'?", "option_A": "None of the others are correct causes.", "option_B": "Shinzo Abe visited Jerusalem in 2018.", "option_C": "Shinzo Abe offered to host a peace summit in 2017.", "option_D": "Shinzo Abe coined the phrase 'a free and open Indo-Pacific'.", "golden_answer": "A"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "f9dc7c07-adb0-426e-8245-dfe2da30d2e8", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Former Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe was assassinated at a campaign rally.'?", "option_A": "Shinzo Abe coined the phrase 'a free and open Indo-Pacific'.", "option_B": "Shinzo Abe returned to office in 2012 and later became the longest-serving prime minister.", "option_C": "Shinzo Abe visited Jerusalem in 2018.", "option_D": "None of the others are correct causes.", "golden_answer": "D"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "85b90b71-fcde-4f94-88b8-7bb69ef9db91", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'A man fired twice at Shinzo Abe.'?", "option_A": "None of the others are correct causes.", "option_B": "Shinzo Abe returned to office in 2012 and later became the longest-serving prime minister.", "option_C": "Shinzo Abe reinterpreted Japan's constitution in 2014.", "option_D": "Shinzo Abe visited Jerusalem in 2018.", "golden_answer": "A"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "774b870d-3388-472e-b8c7-b05c8c4df4dc", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'The shooter used a handmade gun.'?", "option_A": "Shinzo Abe returned to office in 2012 and later became the longest-serving prime minister.", "option_B": "A man fired twice at Shinzo Abe.", "option_C": "None of the others are correct causes.", "option_D": "Shinzo Abe became the deputy chief cabinet secretary in the early 2000s.", "golden_answer": "C"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "6ab33a68-3a0b-46eb-89df-5692cb4de6bf", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Security arrested the suspected gunman, Tetsuya Yamagami.'?", "option_A": "None of the others are correct causes.", "option_B": "Shinzo Abe coined the phrase 'a free and open Indo-Pacific'.", "option_C": "Shinzo Abe promoted the Quadrilateral Security Dialogue (Quad).", "option_D": "Shinzo Abe returned to office in 2012 and later became the longest-serving prime minister.", "golden_answer": "A"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "5d956e6b-95f2-4928-947c-5d382eff0d46", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Security arrested the suspected gunman, Tetsuya Yamagami.'?", "option_A": "Benjamin Netanyahu visited Tokyo in 2014.", "option_B": "Former Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe was assassinated at a campaign rally.", "option_C": "Shinzo Abe visited Jerusalem in 2018.", "option_D": "A man fired twice at Shinzo Abe.", "golden_answer": "B,D"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "b1b1b811-df9d-41be-a1f6-b8d54ecba730", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Security arrested the suspected gunman, Tetsuya Yamagami.'?", "option_A": "Shinzo Abe promoted the Quadrilateral Security Dialogue (Quad).", "option_B": "Former Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe was assassinated at a campaign rally.", "option_C": "Shinzo Abe became the youngest prime minister in postwar Japan in 2006.", "option_D": "Shinzo Abe offered to host a peace summit in 2017.", "golden_answer": "B"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "8f928bf9-dce6-49d0-b18b-cfedc89ba89f", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Explosives were found at Tetsuya Yamagami's home.'?", "option_A": "None of the others are correct causes.", "option_B": "Shinzo Abe became the deputy chief cabinet secretary in the early 2000s.", "option_C": "Shinzo Abe returned to office in 2012 and later became the longest-serving prime minister.", "option_D": "Shinzo Abe coined the phrase 'a free and open Indo-Pacific'.", "golden_answer": "A"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "afd9ca16-e131-4511-9061-a82971e42f04", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Videos of the assassination circulated on social media.'?", "option_A": "Shinzo Abe offered to host a peace summit in 2017.", "option_B": "Shinzo Abe coined the phrase 'a free and open Indo-Pacific'.", "option_C": "None of the others are correct causes.", "option_D": "The shooter used a handmade gun.", "golden_answer": "C"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "30c01d95-fd63-4a6b-843b-a8468a240d38", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Social media companies removed harmful content.'?", "option_A": "Shinzo Abe reinterpreted Japan's constitution in 2014.", "option_B": "None of the others are correct causes.", "option_C": "A man fired twice at Shinzo Abe.", "option_D": "Yoshihide Suga succeeded Shinzo Abe in September 2020.", "golden_answer": "B"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "55f444d0-00c2-4b5a-8222-1f8b677f0a2b", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Social media companies removed harmful content.'?", "option_A": "Shinzo Abe became the youngest prime minister in postwar Japan in 2006.", "option_B": "Videos of the assassination circulated on social media.", "option_C": "Shinzo Abe visited Jerusalem in 2018.", "option_D": "Explosives were found at Tetsuya Yamagami's home.", "golden_answer": "B"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "f53fa15b-809a-4ae9-a6b1-d7fca809ef7d", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Shinzo Abe was pronounced dead at 5:03 p.m.'?", "option_A": "Social media companies removed harmful content.", "option_B": "Security arrested the suspected gunman, Tetsuya Yamagami.", "option_C": "None of the others are correct causes.", "option_D": "Shinzo Abe coined the phrase 'a free and open Indo-Pacific'.", "golden_answer": "C"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "40abcdfd-c1e4-4f53-b92b-1e123fb7ef6e", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Shinzo Abe was pronounced dead at 5:03 p.m.'?", "option_A": "A man fired twice at Shinzo Abe.", "option_B": "Shinzo Abe visited Jerusalem in 2018.", "option_C": "Former Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe was assassinated at a campaign rally.", "option_D": "Security arrested the suspected gunman, Tetsuya Yamagami.", "golden_answer": "A,C"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "c32c574f-1751-4857-ae08-6fa67edd982a", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'Shinzo Abe was pronounced dead at 5:03 p.m.'?", "option_A": "Shinzo Abe became the deputy chief cabinet secretary in the early 2000s.", "option_B": "A man fired twice at Shinzo Abe.", "option_C": "Security arrested the suspected gunman, Tetsuya Yamagami.", "option_D": "Explosives were found at Tetsuya Yamagami's home.", "golden_answer": "B"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "1b050418-aef9-449b-a14b-8dd84a3cdcff", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'World leaders expressed shock and condemned the murder.'?", "option_A": "Shinzo Abe coined the phrase 'a free and open Indo-Pacific'.", "option_B": "Shinzo Abe reinterpreted Japan's constitution in 2014.", "option_C": "Shinzo Abe offered to host a peace summit in 2017.", "option_D": "None of the others are correct causes.", "golden_answer": "D"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "a38210b5-93e5-4ea0-a0bc-5036b2a4a888", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'World leaders expressed shock and condemned the murder.'?", "option_A": "Former Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe was assassinated at a campaign rally.", "option_B": "Benjamin Netanyahu visited Tokyo in 2014.", "option_C": "The shooter used a handmade gun.", "option_D": "Yoshihide Suga succeeded Shinzo Abe in September 2020.", "golden_answer": "A"}
{"topic_id": 4, "uuid": "9f2a97e0-3398-4ecb-99a2-3c7e8a64ea64", "question": "Which of the following options are the causes of the event 'World leaders expressed shock and condemned the murder.'?", "option_A": "The shooter used a handmade gun.", "option_B": "Former Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe was assassinated at a campaign rally.", "option_C": "Social media companies removed harmful content.", "option_D": "Shinzo Abe was pronounced dead at 5:03 p.m.", "golden_answer": "B,D"}
